const Jokes = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "Why do programmers prefer dark mode?",
    answer: "Because light attracts bugs.",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "Why do programmers always mix up Halloween and Christmas?",
    answer: "Because Oct 31 equals Dec 25.",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "How do you know if a programmer is an extrovert?",
    answer: "They constantly talk about their functions.",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "What do you call a snake that works in a computer factory?",
    answer: "A python.",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "Why was the computer cold?",
    answer: "It left its Windows open.",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question:
      "Why did the programmer quit his job at the orange juice factory?",
    answer: "He couldn't handle the constant pressure of the pulp.",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: "What do you call a boomerang that doesn't come back?",
    answer: "A stick.",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "What do you call a programmer who's always late to meetings?",
    answer: 'A "Coder-do"',
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "Why did the programmer quit his job at the juice factory?",
    answer: "He couldn't handle the pressure of the pulp.",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: "What do you call a programmer from Finland?",
    answer: "A Finn-ish coder.",
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    question: "Why do programmers always mix up Halloween and Christmas?",
    answer: "Because Oct 31 equals Dec 25.",
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    question: "Why do programmers prefer dark mode?",
    answer: "Because light attracts bugs.",
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    question: "How do you know if a programmer is an extrovert?",
    answer: "They constantly talk about their functions.",
  },
  {
    id: 14,
    question: "What do you call a snake that works in a computer factory?",
    answer: "A python.",
  },
  {
    id: 15,
    question: "Why was the computer cold?",
    answer: "It left its Windows open.",
  },
  {
    id: 16,
    question:
      "Why did the programmer quit his job at the orange juice factory?",
    answer: "He couldn't handle the constant pressure of the pulp.",
  },
  {
    id: 17,
    question: "Why do programmers always mix up Halloween and Christmas?",
    answer: "Because Oct 31 equals Dec 25.",
  },
  {
    id: 18,
    question: "How do you know if a programmer is an extrovert?",
    answer: "They constantly talk about their functions.",
  },

  {
    id: 19,
    question: "Why did the tomato turn red?",
    answer: "Because it saw the salad dressing!",
  },
  {
    id: 20,
    question: "Why don't scientists trust atoms?",
    answer: "Because they make up everything.",
  },
  {
    id: 21,
    question: "Why was the math book sad?",
    answer: "Because it had too many problems.",
  },
  {
    id: 22,
    question: "Why did the banana go to the doctor?",
    answer: "Because it wasn't peeling well.",
  },
  {
    id: 23,
    question: "Why did the Python programmer quit their job?",
    answer: "They didn't get list-ed.",
  },
  {
    id: 24,
    question: "Why was the JavaScript developer sad?",
    answer: 'Because they didn\'t know how to "null" handle their emotions.',
  },
  {
    id: 25,
    question: "Why did the programmer quit their job as a plumber?",
    answer: "They didn't like debugging pipes.",
  },
  {
    id: 26,
    question: "Why was the programmer always calm during a crisis?",
    answer: 'They always had a "plan B" ready.',
  },
  {
    id: 27,
    question: "What do you call a snake that works in a computer factory?",
    answer: "A python.",
  },
  {
    id: 28,
    question: "Why was the computer cold?",
    answer: "It left its Windows open.",
  },
  {
    id: 29,
    question:
      "Why did the programmer quit his job at the orange juice factory?",
    answer: "He couldn't handle the constant pressure of the pulp.",
  },
  {
    id: 30,
    question: "Why do programmers always mix up Halloween and Christmas?",
    answer: "Because Oct 31 equals Dec 25.",
  },
  {
    id: 31,
    question: "How do you know if a programmer is an extrovert?",
    answer: "They constantly talk about their functions.",
  },
];

export default Jokes;
